paywithatweet.com 2017-06-30

# Pay with a Tweet - Get paid by virality

Last Modified: January 10, 2017

####  1\. Provider

aklamio GmbH, Hagelberger Str. 11, 10965 Berlin ("aklamio") operates the "Pay with a Tweet" on-line service ("Service"). Pay with a Tweet allows registered users to virally market their products and content (e.g. songs, e-Books, white papers and vouchers) via various social networks (e.g. Twitter, Facebook). 

aklamio takes the protection of your personal data very seriously and complies with the applicable data protection regulations, such as the German Federal Data Protection Act (BDSG) and the Telemedia Act (TMG). The following declaration provides an overview of how we guarantee this protection and what kind of data is collected for what purpose. 

####  2\. Personal data

Personal data is only collected, processed and used as described below in the course of its use by Pay with a Tweet. Personal data is any individual information about the personal or material circumstances of a specified or identifiable natural person (excluded: legal entities, such as e.g. a Ltd. or Inc.). Personal data primarily includes details such as a person's name, postal address, e-mail address or professional circumstance.

####  3\. Collection, processing and use of personal data 

When you access Pay with a Tweet websites ([www.paywithatweet.com](http://www.paywithatweet.com/), [www.paywithapost.de](http://www.paywithapost.de/), [www.paywithapost.com](http://www.paywithapost.com/), hereinafter collectively referred to as "Websites"), aklamio will automatically collect information which your browser transmits to us, and save this in its Server Log Files (regardless of whether you are registered with Pay with a Tweet or not). Namely:

  * referrer URL (last visited website);
  * host name of the computer used to access the website (IP address);
  * time of server request;
  * pages visited within [www.paywithatweet.com](http://www.paywithatweet.com/), [www.paywithapost.com](http://www.paywithapost.com/), [www.paywithapost.de](http://www.paywithapost.de/);
  * name of downloaded files and/or information
  * amount of data transmitted
  * operating system and information about the internet browser of the computer used to access the website;
  * http status code (e.g. "Request successful" or "Requested file not found").

When you use Pay with a Tweet functions to post on social networks, aklamio will also collect and store the following additional data:

  * posted text;
  * link to the post;
  * name of the network used;
  * unique ID of the user making the post on the network used;
  * date of post.

It is irrelevant whether the Pay with a Tweet functions are used directly via aklamio's own Websites, or by incorporating a campaign on the customer's website. 

During each posting session on social networks, aklamio will also collect and store the following data, purely temporarily:

  * access information (so-called tokens) for posts on the selected social network;
  * access information (so-called tokens) for viewing the user's last posted links on the selected social network;
  * the date the Pay with a Tweet functions were used.

When you register on Pay with a Tweet websites, aklamio will also collect and store the following data:

  * e-mail address;
  * your chosen password (in encrypted form).

When you use chargeable functions on Pay with a Tweet websites, aklamio will collect and store the following additional data:

  * billing address, including VAT ID no.;
  * billing information (products purchased, prices, date of purchase).

aklamio will only use this data to enable you to access Pay with a Tweet's services, and for the purpose of managing the contractual relationship between you and aklamio. 

We also offer a log in via Facebook Connect for the use of our service. Facebook Connect is a service of Facebook, Inc. (“Facebook”). If you use Facebook Connect, we process and store the data you transmit only for registration purposes. The use of Facebook Connect is subject to the respective Facebook privacy policies and terms of use. When using Facebook Connect, your Facebook profile and public data available on Facebook will be transferred from Facebook to aklamio. For more information about Facebook Connect, please click [here](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/your-info-on-other).

All data is stored on servers located within Europe which are properly supervised and monitored by aklamio. 

As a result of the connection to various social networks which is absolutely necessary for the Service, certain data may also be transmitted to countries outside of Europe (EEA), particularly to the USA (for example Facebook, Twitter) and Russia (VKontakte) (see also Point 7). 

#### 4\. Payment details

If you use chargeable Service upgrades, your payment details will be forwarded to the relevant payment services provider for processing (e.g. Paypal). These partner companies have their own data protection policies. We encourage you to read these policies thoroughly before using the Service, and check that you agree with them. To enable payments to be processed and invoiced when the upgrades are automatically renewed, partner companies store references to payment details (these are primarily e-mail addresses, status information and so-called tokens as a reference to payments via the partner company). The actual payment details (including credit card and bank details) do not pass through aklamio's servers and systems.

#### 5\. Cookies

The Websites use so-called cookies in several places. These help make our service more user-friendly, effective and secure, among other things. Cookies are textual information which a website transmits to the cookie file of the browser on your computer hard drive or other end device, so that the website can remember who you are, among other things. A cookie typically contains the name of the domain from which the cookie originates, the cookies' "lifetime" and a value, usually a unique, randomly generated number. The Pay with a Tweet websites use the following types of cookies: 

Session cookies: these are temporary cookies which remain in your browser's cookie file until you leave the website. Session cookies allow you to be identified for the duration of your visit. This information will not be stored once you have left the website. 

Browser cookies: these remain in your browser's cookie file for longer. How long depends on the "lifetime" of the particular cookie. This may be indefinitely or until its deletion on a specific end date. The reason for using these permanent cookies is to track the provision of services. Permanent cookies do not contain any personal data. Your name, IP address, etc., are not stored. 

If you do not wish to accept our cookies, you can reject them and deny access to previously stored information, by adjusting your web browser settings accordingly. The settings within your web browser enabling you to do this differ from browser to browser, but can generally be found under "Data Protection" or "Cookies" within your browser's "Internet Options" or "Properties" menu. If you need help turning off cookies, you should refer to your browser's "Help" menu. Please note, however, that you may be unable to use the Pay with a Tweet functions properly if cookies are switched off.

#### 6\. Google Analytics

The Websites use Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics also uses cookies (see description in Point 5), which allow your use of the website to be analysed. The information generated by the cookie about your use of this website will usually be transmitted to a Google server in the USA, where it is stored. IP anonymisation has been activated on this website, so that Google abbreviates the user's IP address in advance within Member States of the European Union or in other States party to the Agreement on the European Economic Area. Only in exceptional cases is the full IP address transmitted to a Google server in the USA and abbreviated there. Google will use this information on behalf of aklamio, to evaluate your use of the website, to compile reports about the website activities, and to provide aklamio with other services related to the use of the website and the internet. The IP address transmitted from your browser within the framework of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other Google data. 

You can prevent the storage of the cookies by adjusting your browser software accordingly; we would point out, however, that you may be unable to fully use all the functions of this website in this case. You can also prevent Google from collecting and processing the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the website (including your IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available from the following link: <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=de>.

#### 7\. Connection to social networks

aklamio uses the interfaces of the social networks involved to implement Pay with a Tweet functions. These currently include:

  * Facebook (Facebook Ireland Limited, Hanover Reach, 5-7 Hanover Quay, Dublin 2 Ireland, [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/](http://https//www.facebook.com/about/privacy/))
  * Twitter (Twitter, Inc., Attn: Copyright Agent, 1355 Market Street, Suite 900 San Francisco, CA 94103, <https://twitter.com/privacy>)
  * LinkedIn (LinkedIn Ireland, 70 Sir John Rogerson's Quay, Dublin 2, Ireland, <https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy>)
  * VKontakte (A, 61 Ligovsky av., 191040 Sankt Petersburg, <http://vk.com/privacy>)
  * XING (XING AG, Dammtorstraße 29-32, 20354 Hamburg, Germany h<http://www.xing.com/privacy>)
  * Google (Google Inc. ("Google"), located at 1600 Amphitheatre Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, United States, <https://www.google.com/intl/de/policies/privacy/>)

aklamio reserves the right to increase or reduce the social networks on offer in future without the agreement of Pay with a Tweet users (see Point 15 of our T&Cs). These social networks have their own data protection policies (see above links). We encourage you to read these policies thoroughly before using the Service, and check that you agree with them. 

aklamio does not share its users' personal data with the social networks involved - except for the information stated below. In order to implement the Pay with a Tweet functions, it is, however, necessary for aklamio to transmit the following data to the social networks:

  * user's unique identification on the social network (so-called User ID);
  * links to and posts regarding campaigns used by the user.

If you do not agree to this, you should not use the Service. 

#### 8\. Changes to this data protection policy.

aklamio reserves the right to adapt its security and data protection measures, provided this is necessary as a result of technical or legal developments. In these cases, we will also update our data protection information accordingly. Please make sure, therefore, that you always use the latest version of our data protection declaration.

#### 9\. Questions and contact

If you have any questions regarding the collection, processing or use of your personal data, or to request the disclosure, correction, blocking or deletion of data, please contact [ info@paywithatweet.com](mailto:info@paywithatweet.com).
